{
    "subject": "resource/Vilhelm_Aubert",
    "predicate": "property/workplaces",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Oslo",
    "human_readable": "Vilhelm Aubert worked at the University of Oslo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9867201447486877,
            "question": "What was Vilhelm Aubert's role at the University of Oslo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9682273864746094,
            "question": "Did Vilhelm Aubert collaborate with other researchers at the University of Oslo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.967584490776062,
            "question": "Is Vilhelm Aubert affiliated with the University of Oslo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9544873833656311,
            "question": "What is known about Vilhelm Aubert's background and education prior to working at the University of Oslo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9542862176895142,
            "question": "What field of study is likely related to Vilhelm Aubert's work at the University of Oslo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9436571598052979,
            "question": "How long did Vilhelm Aubert work at the University of Oslo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.928435206413269,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Vilhelm Aubert's contributions to the University of Oslo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.924414336681366,
            "question": "Were there any notable events or research projects associated with Vilhelm Aubert at the University of Oslo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9001189470291138,
            "question": "Where did Vilhelm Aubert work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8348793983459473,
            "question": "What university was associated with Vilhelm Aubert?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vilhelm Aubert worked at the University of Oslo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5173_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Vilhelm Aubert work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5173_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable events or research projects associated with Vilhelm Aubert at the University of Oslo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5173_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Vilhelm Aubert's contributions to the University of Oslo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5173_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5173_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5173_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5173_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5173_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5173_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5173_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5173_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5173_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5173_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5173_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Vilhelm Aubert was a professor at the Faculty of Law, University of Oslo from 1963 to his death, and later at the Department of Sociology from 1971 to 1988."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports this statement. Specifically, multiple documents mention that Vilhelm Aubert was a professor at the Faculty of Law, University of Oslo from 1963 to his death in 1988, which confirms that he worked at the University of Oslo."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}